trimhealthymama.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy Policy – THM.com

Welby Street Press LLC  [“THM”], offers online services designed to provide diet, wellness, fitness, and product-related information and services. Our websites enable persons to access and download information, and to read and post content on our public blogs or forums.

Respect for the privacy of personal information about you is very important to us. THM is committed to collecting, maintaining, and securing personal information about you in accordance with this privacy policy, as well as applicable laws, rules and regulations. This policy applies to personal information collected from THM online services such as websites, email, and other online and downloadable tools that display a link to this policy. This policy does not apply to any website links that are operated by third parties with whom THM has no affiliation or control.

**What is “personal information”?**

Personal information is data that identifies or that is used by THM to identify or contact an individual. Personal information does not include content a subscriber uploads to any THM blog or forum for viewing by the public or other subscribers.

**How does THM collect personal information online?**

THM collects personal information through its online services. THM will collect standard information required to register subscribers to its website, and to collect membership fees or other payments subscribers authorize THM to process. 

There are three methods that THM uses to collect personal information online:

  1. **Information that you provide:** THM collects personal information and other data that you voluntarily enter into forms or data fields on online services. This includes contact information such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, user ID and password, date of birth, and other related information that THM deems appropriate to further the purposes of its online services. THM may also collect information about you that you provide when subscribing to our online services, and may collect credit card information to process those orders.

  2. **Information from public or third party information sources:  **THM may collect personal information from public or third party information sources. When customers use a credit card on our website, THM verifies the validity of the credit card information with financial or credit organizations. In some cases, we may augment our existing user databases with information from third parties. Some of this information may be personal information, such as change of postal address information.

  3. **Information collected from your computer or other electronic device:**  
We may collect information about your computer or other electronic device when you use our online services. This information may include your IP address, domain name, browser type, and date and time of your request. If you use a mobile device to access our online services, we also may collect information about your device, such as your device ID and device type, as well as usage information about your device and your use of our online services.

THM does not use certain tracking technologies that identify you personally such as cookies or pixel tags. However, we may use technologies to remember your personal preferences and selections, or to confirm whether you have read or clicked on certain email communications we send to you so that we can make our communications more useful and interesting to you.

**Does THM collect, use, and disclose personal information?**

THM collects personal information online as necessary to enable individuals to register for, customize, or personalize certain of THM’s online services and communications. THM uses personal information collected online to provide services and features that individuals have requested. However, THM will not sell, rent, or otherwise distribute your personal information to third parties for purposes not otherwise permitted by this Policy.

**Do I have choices about how THM collects, uses, and discloses personal information about me?**

If you do not want THM to collect personal information from you, do not use any THM online services.

**Who will have access to personal information about me**

Personal information about you will be accessible to THM, its subsidiaries or assigns, and to others that use personal information solely for and at the direction of THM. Generally, unless otherwise permitted by this Policy, THM will delete your personal information if you elect to terminate your subscription to any online service.

**Sharing personal information:**

THM does not sell or share personal information about you except as described in this policy. However, THM may decide to reorganize or divest its business through sale, merger or acquisition. If so, personal information may be shared with actual or prospective purchasers. THM will obtain written assurances that personal information will be protected in these circumstances. THM reserves the right to retain and disclose personal information about you for reporting to government authorities or in legal proceedings as authorized or required by applicable law. Except as provided in this policy, personal information about you will not otherwise be shared without your permission.

**Securing personal information?**

THM will take reasonable steps to protect personal information as it is collected and transmitted between your device and our online services and servers, as well as to protect personal information in its possession from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. It is your personal responsibility to secure your own copies of your passwords for our online services.

**Protection of Children**

In general, THM online services are not directed at children and are designed for individuals who are 18 years of age or older.  We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. If you are a parent or guardian that has knowledge that we have collected information from your child, please contact the THM at the address below to request removal.

From time to time, some THM online services may provide features for children. When we do offer those features, we will take appropriate steps to ensure that verifiable parental consent is obtained prior to any collection, use or disclosure of personal information from children.

**May I correct personal information about me?**

To access personal information about you collected online, and to keep it accurate, or to request deletion, you may contact us at the address below.  In some cases we may not be able to delete certain personal information about you. You also may update personal information about you online by modifying information that you previously have entered into forms or data fields on our website. Where permitted by law, your ability to access and correct personal information will be limited where access and correction would: inhibit THM’s ability to comply with a legal or ethical obligation; inhibit THM’s ability to investigate, make, or defend legal claims; result in disclosure of personal information about a third party; or result in breach of a contract or disclosure of trade secrets or other proprietary business information belonging to THM or a third party.

**How long does THM retain personal information?**

We retain personal information for as long as needed for the specific business purpose or purposes for which it was collected. In some cases, we may be required to retain information for a longer period of time based on laws or regulations that apply to our business. Where possible, we try to remove unnecessary identifiers from records that we may need to keep for periods beyond the original retention period.

**What is THM’s contact address for privacy questions?**

Should you have questions about this policy or THM’s information collection, you may contact us via email at the address below. We may contact you for follow-up information and may share your inquiry with other individuals within THM or working for THM that are responsible for functions related to the subject of your inquiry. Except where required by law, THM cannot ensure a response to questions or comments regarding topics unrelated to this policy or THM’s privacy practices. THM’s contact email address is support@trimhealthymama.com.

**Policy updates**

THM reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at its discretion. If we decide to change this policy, we will post those changes at this site so you always will know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. We may also email any modifications. This policy was last updated in August 2015.
